saffranautos.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Saffran

#### Send Inquiry

Please view our Personal Information Collection Statement. By clicking the Submit button you acknowledge that you have read and agree to abide by the Saffranautos Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.

Home __ Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

* * *

| 

Saffranautos.com recognizes the importance of social responsibility that it truthfully work to meet the needs of its customers and to contribute to the society. The Personal Information obtained from its customers in the course of business activities are an important asset of the customers and of Saffranautos.com as it leads to creation of new value. Saffranautos.com protects Personal Information from information security threats with the following Basic Policy and meets its customer's expectations on its reliability As a company, Saffranautos.com is committed to the responsible handling of Personal Information.

(Personal Information Protection Policy)

1\. Saffranautos.com observes the Act on the Protection of Personal Information, Act on the Use of Social Security and Tax Number System in the Administrative Procedure and other relevant laws, rules, and guidelines established by the government and other regulations.  
2\. SAFFRANAUTOS has established a management framework to protect Personal Information, and assigned a person to “Personal Information Protection Administrator” position and implemented the appropriate protection of it.  
3\. SAFFRANAUTOS utilizes Personal Information within the scope of the intended use that is clearly communicated to customers, and takes measures not to be used beyond the scope. SAFFRANAUTOS does not disclose or provide Personal Information provided by customers to third parties except with the consent of the customer from whom the Personal Information was obtained or when there is a legitimate reason.  
4\. SAFFRANAUTOS strives to prevent unauthorized access to Personal Information or the leakage, loss, or damage of Personal Information and continually enhances, re-mediates and manages information security.  
5\. SAFFRANAUTOS responds to inquiries concerning Personal Information or requests from customers for disclosure of their Personal Information sincerely and without delay.  
  
---|---  
  
## 1\. Personal Information

* * *  
  
| 

Personal Information means information concerning a User as an individual, which can identify the User based on the name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, educational institution, or other descriptions, etc. constituting such information. In addition, any information which cannot identify the User solely by itself but can easily be collated with other information and, as a result thereof, can identify the User, is also included in the scope of Personal Information.

*"Personal Information" is described in this Privacy Policy exclude Specific Personal Information, etc.  
  
## 2\. Purpose of Use of Personal Information

* * *  
  
| 

SAFFRANAUTOS will use Personal Information within the scope of the purposes provided in the Purpose of Use. The Purpose of Use is specifically defined and made clear to our customers, and is announced on our website as shown below. SAFFRANAUTOS will make an effort to limit the Purpose of Use according to the situation in which the information is obtained.

  * (1) Achieving the Purpose of Use of our service and business.
  * (2) Notices of service, etc. to its customers.
  * (3) Giving notice to shareholders, provision of various types of information and shareholder management
  * (4) Exercise of rights or performance of obligations based on Act of Japan and other relevant laws and ordinances
  * (5) Responding to inquiries, requests, etc. from its customers
  * (6) Carrying out operations incidental to (1) through (5) above and operations to properly and smoothly manage the business of SAFFRANAUTOS

When handling Personal Information beyond the scope necessary for achieving the Purpose of Use, SAFFRANAUTOS will seek customer’s consent except for cases prescribed under items in Paragraph 3 of Article 16 of the Privacy Act.  
  
## 3\. Provision of Personal Data to Third Parties

* * *  
  
| 

SAFFRANAUTOS will not provide Personal Information to a third party without the customer’s consent, unless where any of the following applies:

  * (1) required under laws or ordinances;
  * (2) required to protect human life, body or asset (including that of legal entities) and difficult to obtain the approval by the customer him/herself;
  * (3) made to a consignee within the scope necessary for carrying out our business
  * (4) to use Personal Information jointly with a group company or a business partner of SAFFRANAUTOS within the scope of the intended use;
  * (5) to provide, in an unrecoverable format, Personal Information in a format that does not allow easy identification or recognition of the corresponding individual.

When handling Personal Information beyond the scope necessary for achieving the Purpose of Use, SAFFRANAUTOS will seek customer’s consent except for cases prescribed under items in Paragraph 3 of Article 16 of the Privacy Act.  
  
## 4\. Disclaimer concerning the provision of Personal Information to third parties

* * *  
  
| 

SAFFRANAUTOS will not be responsible for the acquisition of Personal Information by a third party where any of the following applies:

  * (1) A User indicates his/her own Personal Information to a specific company, using any function under the Services or by other means (As for the handling of Personal Information in the Service Using Companies, etc., please directly make inquiries to each of the Service Using Companies, etc.);
  * (2) A User is unexpectedly identified by information entered by the User under the Services;
  * (3) A User provides Personal Information to, and the User's Personal Information is used at, an external site linked by the Services; or
  * (4) Anyone other than a User obtains the User's information (ID, password, etc.) which can identify the User as an individual.
  * (5) Additionally to above, Personal Information is leaked by computer viruses or similar causes.

## 5\. Supervision of contractors

* * *  
  
| 

SAFFRANAUTOS may consign all or part of our customer’s Personal Information handling operation. In such a case, SAFFRANAUTOS elects a contractor who is expected to properly handle Personal Information, appropriately specify matters concerning handling of Personal Information such as Security Management Measures, confidentiality, terms and conditions of reconsignment, return of Personal Information upon expiration or termination of contract agreement, and performs necessary and appropriate supervision.  
  
## 6\. Handling of Sensitive Information

* * *  
  
| 

SAFFRANAUTOS will not collect, use, or provide to a third party Sensitive Information, including but not limited to information regarding your healthcare or case history, except for cases provided by the Privacy Act, other relevant laws, ordinances and guidelines.  
  
## 7\. Handling of Specific Personal Information, etc.

* * *  
  
| 

The Purpose of Use of Specific Personal Information, etc. is limited under the “My Number” Act, and SAFFRANAUTOS will not collect or use Specific Personal Information, etc. beyond the prescribed Purpose of Use.  
We will not provide Specific Personal Information, etc. to a third party except in cases permitted under the “My Number” Act.  
  
## 8\. Notice of Matters, Disclosure, Amendment, or Suspension of Use of Personal Information and Specific Personal Information, etc.

* * *  
  
| 

Customer requests for any notice of matters, disclosure, amendment, or suspension of use of Personal Information and Specific Personal Information, etc. held by SAFFRANAUTOS under the Privacy Act shall be directed to the "Contact Office" indicated in Clause 11 below. After confirming the customer as the requesting party, the customer is requested to complete a form designated by us. SAFFRANAUTOS will then follow the procedures and, in principle, provide a written response in a proper, timely manner. SAFFRANAUTOS will charge the prescribed fees for responding to a request for any disclosure.  
  
## 9\. Use of Cookies, etc.

* * *  
  
| 

SAFFRANAUTOS uses cookies, etc. to provide better services on its websites.  
  
## 10\. Management of Personal Data and Specific Personal Information, etc.

* * *  
  
| 

SAFFRANAUTOS will take a rational security measures to manage Personal Information and Specific Personal Information, etc. securely and to prevent divulgence, loss or damage to Personal Information and Specific Personal Information, etc. handled by SAFFRANAUTOS, and will ensure the accuracy and prompt updating of Personal Information and Specific Personal Information, etc. which are necessary to achieve the Purpose of Use.  
  
## News

  * **10 Things every car owner should know!!**

While driver s education may teach a person how to drive, they don t always teach everything a person needs to know about their car. Part of this is because things differ from brand to brand and model to model. Here are ten different things that all drivers need to know how to do in order to keep their car running longer. These things can also h...

Read More 
    * **No More Boring Cars for Toyota!!**

Akio Toyoda has issued a company wide decree for "no more boring cars." And to back it up, the Toyota Motor Corp. President has given designers greater clout than ever. The shift of power away from engineers delivered its first daring design in the futuristic, fin-tailed 2016 Prius. The latest is the 2018 Camry sedan, with its bold proportions and...

Read More 
      * **Audi Promotes Gender Equality.**

Audi is using its Super Bowl ad to promote gender pay equality via a tale about a father and daughter in the latest example of a marketer linking itself to female empowerment. The 60-second spot, which was released Wednesday, is called "Daughter" and shows a dad pondering how society will value his daughter worth as he looks on while his young c...

Read More 

back to top

### Get the Latest Saffranautos® News & Updates!

Copyright 2017 Saffran Autos all rights reserved. 

Copyright 2017 Saffran Autos all rights reserved.
